{
    "id": "c42b3a305d0b41c2982a81cea9b5bb6d",
    "title": "Can, may and could worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "a09cafaafc9c4ba49c31ae2c1a41cb3a",
            "title": "Can, May, And Could",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He ……………….. be on holiday, but I’m not sure.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "may",
                        "can",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ……………….. be right, but I would still like to check.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "may",
                        "can",
                        "should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………. you turn down the volume, please?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Can",
                        "May",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ……………… go when you have finished.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "may",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ……………….. ask whatever questions you have.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "may",
                        "can",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ………………… smoke in the kitchen.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "must not",
                        "cannot",
                        "should not",
                        "All of the above"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "From his accent, he ………………….. be from Toronto.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘Who can it be?’ ‘It ……………….. the postman.’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "may not",
                        "cannot",
                        "must not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The weather ……………… be hotter tomorrow.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "may",
                        "could",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………. you dance?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Can",
                        "May",
                        "Could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}